Viewers all over the world, wherever you are, Jesus can see you.
See what Jesus can do.
He can liberate you, set your free, heal and deliver you
Get ready! In the name of Jesus be delivered!
Be delivered!
In the name of Jesus!
I can see you being delivered!
Receive faith to put a demand.
Pray along with Prophet T.B Joshua. Touch your screen by faith in Jesus Name.
The presence of God is so thick, it is like a cloud
Right now receive faith and put a demand
Pray along with Prophet T.B Joshua. Touch your screen by faith in Jesus Name.
Put a demand on the anointing that breaks the yoke.
In the name of Jesus!
Pray along with Prophet T.B Joshua. Touch your screen by faith in Jesus Name.
I can see Jesus is reliable. He's faithful. He's just.
Be healed in the name of Jesus!
Be delivered in the name of Jesus!
Be set free in the name of Jesus!
I rescue your career.
Career be rescued!
I rescue your future.
Your future be rescued in the name of Jesus!
Your business, finances, be rescued!
Your business, finances, be rescued in the name of Jesus!
Pray along with Prophet T.B Joshua. Touch your screen by faith in Jesus Name.
We believe that you have been inspired but the clip that you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today
and stay up to date with the latest prophecies, deliverances, service, and testimonies.
From the Synagogue Church Of All Nations
Emmanuel Tv. Changing lives, changing nations, and changing the world.